https://www.nasponline.org/utility/privacy-policy

Contact Us
We respect your privacy. Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address will not be intentionally released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of our organization except as noted below.  NASP reserves the right at any time and without notice to change this Privacy Policy simply by posting such changes on our website. Any such changes will be effective immediately upon posting.
With Whom Do We Share the Personal Information We Collect Through This Site?
Our Service Providers We may share your personal information with companies (including our affiliates) that perform services on our behalf, for example, companies that help process credit card payments. Our service providers are required by contract to protect the confidentiality of the personal information we share with them and to use it only to provide specific services on our behalf.
Select Business Partners In some instances, member names and mailing addresses may be shared for one-time use with select business partners whose products are believed to be of value to members.
Business Transfers Your personal information may be transferred to another entity (either an affiliated entity or an unrelated third party) in connection with a merger, reorganization, dissolution, or similar corporate event. If such a transfer were ever to occur, the acquiring entity’s use of your personal information will still be subject to this Privacy Policy.
Government and Legal Disclosures We may disclose the personal information we collect through this site, when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law (or a court order or subpoena); to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to enforce our terms and conditions or other agreements that govern your use of this site; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of our company, our users, or others.
External Sites The NASP website contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website for which NASP has no responsibility. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information. Additionally, you are not permitted to deep-link to any portion of this website unless such deep-linking is for a legitimate non-commercial, educational purpose. Additionally, you are not permitted to “frame”, “mirror” or otherwise incorporate any part of this website into any other website without our prior written authorization.
Cookies
A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows us to recognize you each time you visit this site (personalization, etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and we do not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by third party content providers, such as newsfeeds.
Remember the Risks Whenever You Use the Internet
While we have taken steps to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition, other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through our site have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
